Shen Gu.
구쉔.
What did you wish for?
무엇을 원하셨나요?
My wish...
내 소원은...
Where are you going to hang it?
어디에 걸어둘 건가요?
Don't take my things.
내 물건을 가져가지 마세요.
Don't take my jade.
내 옥을 가져가지 마세요.
That's Mr. Shen's token for Miss Lin.
그것은 Miss Lin을 위한 Mr. Shen의 토큰입니다.
It's an heirloom jade of the Shen family.
가보 옥이에요 쉔 가문 출신.
Grandfather.
할아버지.
Are you alright, Grandfather?
괜찮으세요, 할아버지?
Where did you
넌 어디서 왔니
get it?
알겠어?
A collector in Shen City
Shen City의 수집가
invited me to his house.
나를 그의 집에 초대했습니다.
I spotted this jade at once.
나는 단번에 이 옥을 발견했다.
It's broken,
고장났어요
but the owner went to great lengths
그런데 주인이 애를 많이 썼어요
to restore it.
그것을 복원합니다.
You can tell how much it meant to them.
그것이 그들에게 얼마나 의미가 있었는지 알 수 있습니다.
For some reason,
어떤 이유에서인지
I just felt a strong connection to it.
나는 그것과 강한 연관성을 느꼈습니다.
This jade is my family heirloom.
이 옥은 우리 가족의 가보입니다.
Today, I give it to you
오늘은 너에게 줄게
as a token of my heart.
내 마음의 표시로.
It's really meant for you.
그것은 정말로 당신을 위한 것입니다.
Grandfather.
할아버지.
If you like it, you can have it.
당신이 그것을 좋아한다면, 당신은 그것을 가질 수 있습니다.
Keep it. It'll protect you.
유지하세요. 그것은 당신을 보호할 것입니다.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Mr. Xu, the ladder is here.
Xu 씨, 사다리가 여기 있어요.
You have to hang the wish yourself for it to count.
소원은 직접 걸어야지 계산할 수 있도록.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Careful.
주의 깊은.
I'll hold it steady for you.
나는 당신을 위해 그것을 안정적으로 유지합니다.
Grandfather.
할아버지.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=갱 시티의 메아리=
=Episode 12= (Heart Coming Alive)
=에피소드 12= (심장이 살아난다)
It's been a long time since I've been back.
오랜만이야 내가 돌아온 이후로.
Slow down.
천천히 하세요.
What's wrong?
무슨 일이야?
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
This building dates back to the Republican era.
이 건물의 역사는 공화당 시대로.
It belonged to someone who once helped Grandfather.
그것은 누군가의 것이었습니다 한때 할아버지를 도왔던 사람.
After a fire
화재 발생 후
took their lives,
목숨을 잃었어
Grandfather went through a lot to buy it back
할아버지 고생이 많으셨어요 다시 사려고
and restore it
복원하고
to what it is now.
지금은 무엇입니까?
How is it? Beautiful?
어때요? 아름다운?
I'll show you around.
내가 주변을 보여주지.
Watch your step, Mr. Xu.
발걸음 조심하세요, Xu 씨.
You brought him to the old family home.
당신이 그를 데려왔어 옛 가족의 집으로.
Looks like you're very satisfied with Shen Gu.
매우 만족하신 것 같습니다 구쉔과 함께.
Every time I see him,
그 사람을 볼 때마다
I feel like
내 기분은
(As Long As You Are Back) everything was meant to be.
(당신이 돌아오는 한) 모든 것이 그럴 예정이었습니다.
Grandfather.
할아버지.
Wanxin,
완신,
settle Shen Gu in here.
Shen Gu를 여기에 정착시키세요.
I'm meeting Qingniao Group's president
Qingniao Group 회장님을 만나요
at 2 PM.
오후 2시에.
That's great.
훌륭해요.
I wanted to thank him in person.
나는 그에게 직접 감사를 표하고 싶었다.
I'll go prepare a gift.
선물 준비하러 갈게요.
No need.
필요하지 않습니다.
I've taken care of it.
내가 처리했어.
You two just got married. No need to hover around me all day.
너희 둘은 방금 결혼했어. 하루 종일 내 주위를 맴돌 필요가 없습니다.
Go back to your room and rest.
방으로 돌아가서 휴식을 취하세요.
Changhe, let's go.
창허야, 가자.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Grandfather.
할아버지.
(As Long As You Are Back)
(당신이 돌아오는 한)
I'll take you around.
내가 데려다줄게
I just landed here.
방금 여기에 도착했어요.
There are things at the office I need to handle.
사무실에 물건이 있어요 내가 처리해야 해요.
How about tonight?
오늘 밤은 어때요?
It's fine. Work comes first.
괜찮습니다. 일이 먼저입니다.
Will you be back for dinner?
저녁 먹으러 다시 올래?
Yes.
예.
I'll get going.
나는 갈 것이다.
Go on.
계속하세요.
Boss,
보스,
back to the office as fast as possible.
최대한 빨리 사무실로 돌아가세요.
Don't keep Grandfather waiting.
할아버지를 기다리게 하지 마세요.
Yes.
예.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Welcome to Qingniao Group, Mr. Xu.
Xu씨, Qingniao Group에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
Our chairman has been expecting you.
우리 회장님은 당신을 기다리고 있었습니다.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Mr. Changhe, please have a seat here.
창허씨, 여기 앉으세요.
I didn't expect
기대하지 않았어
Qingniao's president and I
Qingniao 사장과 나
to walk out of the same house just now.
지금 당장 같은 집에서 나가려고요.
I'm sorry, Grandfather.
죄송해요, 할아버지.
I haven't had the chance
기회가 없었어
to tell Wanxin yet.
아직 Wanxin에게 말해야 해요.
Minghui does have a good prospect,
Minghui는 좋은 전망을 갖고 있어요
but it shouldn't have been Qingniao's first choice.
하지만 그러지 말았어야 했어 Qingniao의 첫 번째 선택.
If you're the president,
당신이 대통령이라면,
then it all makes sense.
그러면 모든 것이 이해가 됩니다.
Not entirely because of Wanxin.
전적으로 Wanxin 때문은 아닙니다.
Her father had already been in contact with us before he passed.
그녀의 아버지는 이미 연락을 하고 있었다 그가 지나가기 전에 우리와 함께.
I've always been the one
난 언제나 그랬어
handling the cooperation.
협력을 처리합니다.
Why didn't you tell Wanxin
Wanxin에게 왜 말하지 않았나요
you're the president?
당신이 대통령이에요?
At first, I just wanted to help her through the crisis.
처음에는 그냥 도와주고 싶었어요 위기를 통해.
I didn't expect her to propose.
나는 그녀가 프로포즈할 거라고는 예상하지 못했다.
I couldn't refuse.
나는 거절할 수 없었다.
After that,
그 후
I never found the right moment to tell her.
난 적절한 순간을 찾지 못했어 그녀에게 말하려고.
You should tell her soon.
빨리 그녀에게 말해야 해요.
Don't let it come between you.
그것이 당신 사이에 오도록 두지 마십시오.
I understand, Grandfather.
알겠습니다, 할아버지.
When you left Gang City,
Gang City를 떠났을 때,
you had nothing.
당신에게는 아무것도 없었습니다.
You must've suffered a lot
고생이 많으셨겠군요
to get where you are now.
지금 있는 곳으로 가기 위해.
Come and sit.
와서 앉으세요.
Tell me everything.
나에게 모든 것을 말해주세요.
I, Shen Gu, take thee, Xu Wanxin,
나 Shen Gu가 너를 Xu Wanxin으로 데려가
to be my lawful wedded wife.
나의 합법적인 아내가 되는 것입니다.
(Gang City Marriage Registry)
(갱시티 혼인신고소)
- I do.
- 그래요.
♪A lonely bench on the street corner♪
♪길모퉁이의 쓸쓸한 벤치♪
♪Where all feelings come to rest♪
♪모든 감정이 쉼을 얻는 곳♪
♪In the night sky, the moon's trail♪
♪밤하늘에 달의 흔적♪
♪Stitches up and soothes my sorrow♪
♪꿰매어 슬픔을 달래줍니다♪
♪The courage to get close to you♪
♪당신에게 다가가는 용기♪
♪Drives away my hesitation♪
♪머뭇거림을 없애줍니다♪
♪Fate turns and brings us together♪
♪운명은 변하고 우리를 하나로 묶습니다♪
♪I search my memories with all my might♪
♪기억을 있는 힘껏 찾아본다♪
♪Love catches me off guard♪
♪사랑은 나를 당황하게 만든다♪
♪You, in the album♪
♪앨범 속 당신♪
♪Shine through my past like starlight♪
♪별빛처럼 내 과거를 빛나게 해주세요♪
♪You fall between light and shadow♪
♪당신은 빛과 그림자 사이에 있습니다♪
♪Melting all my fears away♪
♪내 모든 두려움을 녹여버리네요♪
♪Those youthful, naive memories are more than enough to heal♪
♪그 젊고 순진한 기억들 치유하기에 충분해요♪
♪I'm lost in them♪
♪그들에게 푹 빠졌어요♪
♪The world suddenly has meaning♪
♪세상이 갑자기 의미를 갖게 되었습니다♪
♪Through the pouring rain, I found you♪
♪폭우 속에서 당신을 찾았습니다♪
♪In the space of our embrace♪
♪우리 포옹의 공간에서♪
♪Stars spill across the sky♪
♪하늘에 별이 쏟아진다♪
Grandfather,
할아버지,
you've just recovered.
당신은 방금 회복되었습니다.
Let's head back
돌아가자
and rest.
그리고 휴식.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Come back to the family house
가족의 집으로 돌아와
and have dinner together.
그리고 함께 저녁을 먹어요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Grandfather.
할아버지.
Sorry to interrupt.
방해해서 죄송합니다.
Nice to meet you, Grandfather.
만나서 반가워요, 할아버지.
Sorry, I need to borrow Shen Gu.
미안해요, Shen Gu를 빌려야 해요.
We've got a major decision to make.
우리는 중대한 결정을 내려야 합니다.
You're the son of the Fang family, right?
당신은 Fang 가문의 아들입니다. 그렇죠?
Yes.
예.
You're right.
당신 말이 맞아요.
I'm Hongsheng.
저는 홍성이에요.
I'm Qingniao's CFO and legal director.
저는 Qingniao의 CFO이자 법률 이사입니다.
I'm also his partner.
나도 그의 파트너야.
Good.
좋은.
You're following in your dad's footsteps.
당신은 팔로우 중입니다 네 아버지의 발자취.
But you've got your mom's looks.
그런데 넌 엄마의 외모를 갖고 있구나.
My mother is pretty.
우리 엄마는 예뻐요.
So you're saying you're good-looking?
그럼 잘생겼다는 말인가요?
Very well.
아주 좋습니다.
It's happy to see by his side.
그의 옆에 있는 것을 보니 반갑습니다.
Please don't say that.
그런 말은 하지 마세요.
There are other partners too.
다른 파트너도 있습니다.
But we started the company together.
하지만 우리는 함께 회사를 시작했습니다.
He can't do without me.
그는 나 없이는 할 수 없습니다.
Shen Gu is a lucky man.
Shen Gu는 운이 좋은 사람입니다.
Grandfather. Mr. Changhe.
할아버지. 창허 씨.
How was it?
어땠나요?
How did the meeting go?
회의는 어떻게 진행됐나요?
What do you think
어떻게 생각하세요
Qingniao's president is like?
Qingniao의 대통령은 어떤가요?
I've heard he's young,
그 사람이 어리다고 들었는데,
but he makes rare public appearances.
하지만 그는 공개적으로는 거의 모습을 드러내지 않습니다.
Not much is known about him.
그에 대해 알려진 바는 많지 않습니다.
But to build a company like this,
하지만 이런 회사를 만들려면
he must be exceptional.
그는 예외적이어야합니다.
He is young and capable.
그는 젊고 능력이 있다.
He chose to keep investing
그는 계속 투자하기로 결정했습니다
and support us publicly
공개적으로 우리를 지지해 주세요
at our lowest point.
우리의 가장 낮은 지점에서.
He's a man of loyalty.
그는 충성심이 강한 사람입니다.
Mr. Xu, Wan Xin.
Xu 씨, Wan Xin.
Today
오늘
is a good day.
좋은 날입니다.
I've had the kitchen prepare
주방에 준비를 시켰어요
your favorite dishes.
당신이 가장 좋아하는 요리.
Make sure you eat well.
꼭 잘 드세요.
Thank you, Mr. Changhe.
감사합니다, 창허 씨.
Changhe,
창허,
since I'm already in Shen City...
난 이미 Shen City에 있으니까...
Say no more.
더 이상 말하지 마세요.
I know what you want.
나는 당신이 원하는 것을 알고 있습니다.
You could've come yourself.
당신이 직접 올 수도 있었어요.
I wanted to be with her alone.
나는 그녀와 단 둘이 있고 싶었다.
She just wouldn't see me.
그녀는 나를 보지 않을 것입니다.
You're not trying hard enough.
당신은 충분히 열심히 노력하고 있지 않습니다.
There was also a time when you couldn't get to meet with Xu Wanxin.
그러지 못할 때도 있었지 Xu Wanxin을 만나세요.
She's here.
그녀는 여기 있습니다.
Long time no see, Miss Su.
오랜만이에요, 미스 수.
Congratulations, Best Actress Su.
축하합니다, 최우수 여배우 수.
Thank you, Lawyer Fang.
감사합니다, 팽 변호사님.
No, no. Please come in.
아니, 아니. 들어오세요.
Please, this way.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
What's wrong?
무슨 일이야?
It's so hard to get a meeting with you.
당신과의 만남이 너무 어렵습니다.
Who's the one who needs help here?
여기서 도움이 필요한 사람은 누구입니까?
Of course, he's the one asking you.
물론, 그는 당신에게 묻는 사람입니다.
I've got photos of international star Su Mei.
사진이 있어요 국제적인 스타 수 메이의.
Tomorrow's headline is secured.
내일의 헤드라인은 확보되었습니다.
Look.
바라보다.
I know you like this.
나는 당신이 이것을 좋아한다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
I had it prepared for you.
나는 당신을 위해 그것을 준비했습니다.
Grandfather,
할아버지,
you can eat more, but go easy on the alcohol.
더 먹어도 되고, 하지만 술은 가볍게 마시세요.
You've just recovered. You have to be careful.
당신은 방금 회복되었습니다. 조심해야합니다.
My granddaughter is so sweet.
내 손녀는 너무 사랑스러워요.
Have Shen Gu's room at the old family house been arranged?
Shen Gu의 방을 이용하세요 오래된 집에 마련됐나요?
Yes. The guest room is ready.
예. 객실이 준비되었습니다.
How can a newlywed couple
신혼부부는 어떻게
sleep separately?
따로 자?
Right. We're married.
오른쪽. 우리는 결혼했어요.
I'll accept any condition.
나는 어떤 조건이라도 받아들일 것이다.
Consider it my wedding gift to you.
내가 당신에게 주는 결혼 선물이라고 생각하세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Where's mine?
내 건 어딨어?
Are you married?
결혼하셨나요?
How about
How about
I give you my congratulations?
는 어때요? 축하드려요?
No need.
필요하지 않습니다.
You guys chat.
여러분, 채팅하세요.
I'll take off.
나는 이륙할 것이다.
Something came up?
무슨 일이 일어났나요?
I'm staying at the Xu residence tonight.
나는 오늘 밤 Xu 거주지에 머물 예정이다.
No one asks.
아무도 묻지 않습니다.
Has he been like this lately?
그 사람 최근에도 그랬나요?
It's not even that bad today.
오늘은 그다지 나쁘지도 않습니다.
Usually, he's showing off everywhere.
보통 그는 어디에서나 과시합니다.
I'm the biggest victim.
제가 가장 큰 피해자입니다.
Are you hungry?
배고프나요?
Let's eat.
먹자.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Take the seat of honor.
명예의 자리에 앉으십시오.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
It's nothing.
그것은 아무것도 아니다.
Here, try this first.
자, 이것을 먼저 시도해 보세요.
Cheese pumpkin.
치즈 호박.
(Xu Wanxin) (How can you tell)
(쉬완신) (어떻게 알 수 있나요)
(if someone likes you?)
(누군가 당신을 좋아한다면?)
(Xi) (When a guy and a girl)
(시) (남자와 여자일 때)
(start testing each other.)
(서로 테스트를 시작하세요.)
(Why?)
(왜?)
(Feeling a spark?)
(불꽃이 느껴지나요?)
(Let me guess.)
(내가 추측해 보자.)
(It's someone close to you.)
(가까운 사람이에요.)
(His name is Shen Gu.)
(그의 이름은 Shen Gu입니다.)
(Xu Wanxin) (Nice guess.)
(쉬완신) (좋은 추측입니다.)
(Xi: Hey, Wanxin. Are you falling for Shen Gu?)
(시: 안녕, 완신. Shen Gu에게 반하고 있나요?)
Hello?
안녕하세요?
You're back?
돌아왔나요?
I'm downstairs.
나는 아래층에 있습니다.
Want to grab a late-night bite?
늦은 밤에 한 입 먹고 싶나요?
Sure.
확신하는.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪오늘밤 비가 천천히 내린다♪
♪Blending with letters left unread drifting through the air♪
♪읽지 않은 글자와 혼합 공중을 떠다니는 중♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪돌아서 나를 돌아봐♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears quietly appear♪
♪같은 눈에 익숙한 눈물이 조용히 나타나세요♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪너무 많이 짊어진 것 같은 느낌♪
♪So many questions time itself could not make clear♪
♪시간 자체에 질문이 너무 많아요 명확하게 말할 수 없었어요♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪당신이 내 인생에 들어온 순간♪
♪Every dream I had became something I want with you near♪
♪내가 가졌던 모든 꿈은 무언가가 되었어요 가까이에 있고 싶다♪
♪How many letters have I written just for you?♪
♪나는 얼마나 많은 편지를 썼는가 당신을 위해서요?♪
♪If only you could truly hear what my heart is trying to say♪
♪진심으로 들을 수 있다면 내 마음이 말하려는 것♪
♪From this life on no distance could keep us apart♪
♪이생부터 어떤 거리도 우리를 갈라놓을 수 없어요♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪우리가 한 약속♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled one day♪
♪성취할 길을 찾을 것이다 어느 날♪
♪But I want more than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪하지만 난 더 원해요 그 찰나의 시선보다♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪아직도 당신의 대답을 듣지 못했습니다♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending we face?♪
♪아직 엔딩을 다시 쓸 수 있을까요? 우리는?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you will hear it all♪
♪후회가 당신 주위에 돌기 시작할 때 다 들어줄게♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪
♪나를 당신에게 다시 데려가는 모든 것♪